let savollar6 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "advantage",
        answer: "B. ustunlik",
        options: [
            "A. doimiylik",
            "B. ustunlik",
            "C. daromad",
            "D. foydali"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to cause",
        answer: "A. sabab bo'lmoq",
        options: [
            "A. sabab bo'lmoq",
            "B. ilgari surmoq",
            "C. rag'batlantirmoq",
            "D. to'sqinlik qilmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "choice",
        answer: "C. tanlov",
        options: [
            "A. qaror",
            "B. saralash",
            "C. tanlov",
            "D. ovoz berish"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "community",
        answer: "D. jamiyat",
        options: [
            "A. jamiyat",
            "B. guruh",
            "C. jamoa",
            "D. aholi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "dead",
        answer: "A. o'lgan",
        options: [
            "A. o'lgan",
            "B. ko'milgan",
            "C. kasal",
            "D. jarohatli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "distance",
        answer: "C. masofa",
        options: [
            "A. yo'nalish",
            "B. uzunlik",
            "C. masofa",
            "D. yo'l"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to escape",
        answer: "D. qochib qutulmoq",
        options: [
            "A. himoyalanmoq",
            "B. tark etmoq",
            "C. uzoqqa bormoq",
            "D. qochib qutulmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "to face",
        answer: "B. duch kelmoq",
        options: [
            "A. uchratmoq",
            "B. duch kelmoq",
            "C. o'girilmoq",
            "D. e'tiborsiz qolmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "to follow",
        answer: "A. ortidan bormoq",
        options: [
            "A. ortidan bormoq",
            "B. birga yurmoq",
            "C. ortga qaytmoq",
            "D. yugurmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "fright",
        answer: "B. qo'rquv",
        options: [
            "A. qiziquvchanlik",
            "B. qo'rquv",
            "C. iztirob",
            "D. g'azab"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "ghost",
        answer: "D. rux",
        options: [
            "A. maxluq",
            "B. jodugar",
            "C. o'lik",
            "D. rux"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "individual",
        answer: "C. kishi",
        options: [
            "A. guruh",
            "B. oila",
            "C. kishi",
            "D. jamoa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "pet",
        answer: "A. uy hayvoni",
        options: [
            "A. uy hayvoni",
            "B. parranda",
            "C. qush",
            "D. chorva"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "to reach",
        answer: "B. yetib bormoq",
        options: [
            "A. uddalamoq",
            "B. yetib bormoq",
            "C. payqamoq",
            "D. yutmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to return",
        answer: "A. qaytmoq",
        options: [
            "A. qaytmoq",
            "B. yetib kelmoq",
            "C. jo'namoq",
            "D. bormoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "to survive",
        answer: "C. tirik qolmoq",
        options: [
            "A. zabt etmoq",
            "B. yashamoq",
            "C. tirik qolmoq",
            "D. hursand bo'lmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "upset",
        answer: "A. xafa",
        options: [
            "A. xafa",
            "B. havotirlangan",
            "C. qo'rquvga tushgan",
            "D. g'azablangan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "voice",
        answer: "B. ovoz",
        options: [
            "A. vosita",
            "B. ovoz",
            "C. musiqa",
            "D. shovqin"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "weather",
        answer: "D. ob-havo",
        options: [
            "A. iqlim",
            "B. harorat",
            "C. fasl",
            "D. ob-havo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "wise",
        answer: "C. dono",
        options: [
            "A. sergak",
            "B. odobli",
            "C. dono",
            "D. hushyor"
        ]
    }
];
